Guide to the Office of Administration and Facilities, Eileen Buckley 1959-1995 (Bulk 1964-1989) RG 8.0 RG 8.0
New York University Archives
- Series I: General Files
  - Contracts: Dental Center - Residence Hall and Garage Planning, undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Contracts: Dental Center - Residence Hall and Garage Planning, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Contracts: Dental Center - Residence Hall Financing-Dormitory Authority, undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Contracts: Dental Center - Residence Hall Financing-Federal, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Contracts: Dental Center - Residence Hall Parking Facility, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Contracts: Dental Center - Residence Hall Phipps Plaza Lease, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Contracts: Dental Center - Support for Facilities, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058440 4
  - Contracts: Dental Education Facility - Planning and Design, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Contracts: Dental Education Facility - Project Budgets, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Contracts: Dental Education Facility - Project Zoning, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Contracts: Dental Science Building - Construction, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Contracts: Dental Science Building - Construction, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Contracts: Dental Science Building - Construction Costs, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Contracts: Dental Science Building - Equipment, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Contracts: Dental Science Building - Financing, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Contracts: Dental Science Building - P.J. Carlin, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - A Series, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - A Series, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - A Series Bond Issue, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - A and B Series Bond Issue, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - B Series Bond Issue, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - Bond Issue Note Resoultion, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - Bond Issue Series C, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authoirty - Bond Issue Series C-Second, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - Bond Issue Series C-Third, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058441 2
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - Bond Issue Series C, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - C Series Mr. O'Mara, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - C & A Series Reserves, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - Collateralization Issue+D408, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - Cogeneration Project, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - D Series, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - D.A. Bond Issue, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - D.A. Bond Issue, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - D Series Authority Financing, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - D Series Construction, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - D Series Operational, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - E Series Merrill Hall, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - Environmental Assessment Forms, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058442 0
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - F Series, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - F Series, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - Financing, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - Financing, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - General, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - Graduate Law School, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - Hospital Information System, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - Loew Hall Bond Issue, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - Lombard-Wall, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - Medical Hall Bond Issue, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Contracts: Dormitory Authority - Note Resolution, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Contracts: Farkas Building Financing, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058443 8
  - Contracts: Farkas Building Planning and Design, 1961-1964 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Contracts: Farkas Building Planning and Design, 1965-1969 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Contracts: Farkas Building Planning and Design, 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Contracts: Farkas Building Planning and Design, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Contracts: Farkas Education Building Summary of Construction Costs, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Contracts: Farkas Building Zoning Variance, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Contracts: Financing - Federal Governement - Higher Educational Facilities Act, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Contracts: Fourth Street - 15-19 West, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Contracts: Franchise Street Crossing, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Contracts: Loeb Student Center Addition, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Contracts: Loeb Study, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Alterations, undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Architects Agreement, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Auxillary Pavillion, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Basic Science Center, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Cancer Center, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Clinical Research Building, undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Coca-Cola Center, undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Cooperative Care Building, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Cooperative Care Building, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Cooperative Care - Citibank, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Cooperative Care - Closing, undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Cooperative Care - Construction, undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Cooperative Care - Contracts, Correspondence, Minutes, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Cooperative Care - Equitable, undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Cooperative Care - Tishman/Construction, undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
    barcode: 3 1142 4058443 8
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Cooperative Care - Tishman/Construction 2, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058444 6
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Coronary Care Unit, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Emergency Generator, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Institute for Urban Affairs Proposal, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Invitations, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Kips Bay Rentals, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Lecture Hall, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Master Plan, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Master Plan, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Master Plan, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Medical Practice Building, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Millhauser Research Labs, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Outside Space, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Projects, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Projects - Lecture Hall - Architect's Fees, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Proposed Administration Building, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Real Estate, undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Contracts: Medical Center - Site Improvements, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Contracts: Patricia Murphy Restaurant, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Contracts: Penthouse Expense, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Contracts: Sullivan Street Underground Structure, undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Contracts: Thames Street Survey, undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Contracts: Tisch Building Budgets, undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Contracts: Tisch Hall - Claims, undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Contracts: Tisch Hall - Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Contracts: Tisch Hall - Correspondence, 1966-1974 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Contracts: Tisch Hall - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Contracts: Tisch Hall - Sandstone, undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Contracts: Tisch Hall - Summary of Construction Costs, undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Contracts: Tisch Hall - Tisch - McCormick, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058445 3
  - Cook, Samuel Dubois, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Cooke, Lloyd, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Cooper, Richard B., undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Cooper Square, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Cooper Square Blueprints, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Cooper Square Blueprints, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Cooper Square General, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Cooper Square Three, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Cooper Union, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Cooperative Care - Huntington, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Core Curriculum Committee, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - General, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - General, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - General, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - General, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - General, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - General, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - General, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - General, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence - General, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - General, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence - General, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence - General, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence - General, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence - General, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence - General, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence - General, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence - General, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Cost Projections, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Council on Community Service, undated (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Council on European Studies, undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Crane, Allison, undated (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Creative Arts Team, undated (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Cronin, Anthony, undated (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Cross - School Advisement, undated (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Cross - School Advisement, undated (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Cultural Announcements, undated (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Cultural Institutions, undated (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Culture Committee, undated (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Curricular Development Challenge Fund, undated (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Curricular Development Fund, undated (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - D and L Company, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058446 1
  - Daedealus, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Dalton School, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Dalton School, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Dalton School, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Danahar, David, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Daniels, Lee, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Darnowski, Vincent S., undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Davis, Douglass, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Davis, Earl, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Deans Meeting, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Deans Meeting, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Deans Meeting, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Deans Meeting, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Deans Meeting, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Deans Meeting, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Decarvo, Edward, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Deluca, Margaret, undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Deming, W. Edwards, undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Dental Center Physical Therapy, undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Dental Center Sakalid Suggested Improvements, undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Department of Education, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Derry - Londonderry Proposal, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Dew, Edward, undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Diamond, Daniel, undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Diggery, Terrance, undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Dilorenzo, Lorreta, undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Dimetros, Fiseha, undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Distinguished Teaching Awards, undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Distinguished Teaching Awards, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Distinguished Teaching Awards Luncheon, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Distinguished Teaching Medal, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Doctoro, E.L., undated (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Doling, Geraldine, undated (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Donahue, Dennis, undated (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Donoso, Jose, undated (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Dorot Fellowship, undated (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Dorset Hotel, undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Drew University, undated (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Drug and Alcohol, undated (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Drug Free Workplace, undated (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Drysdale, Thomas, undated (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Duchess, Property, undated (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - East Manhattan School, undated (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Education Block, undated (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Edmundson, Lorna, undated (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Educational Leadership Program, undated (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Edwards, Flora, undated (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Ehrenkranz, Shirley, undated (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Eigth Street - 50 East, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Eighty First Street - 14, undated (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Ellis Island, undated (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Ellis Island Project, undated (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Ellis Island Project, undated (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Ellis Island Restoration Commission, undated (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Emory University, undated (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Endara, Guiermo D., undated (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Enhancing the Role of the University, undated (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Environment - Earth Day, undated (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Environmental Books, undated (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - ESA Summary Plan Description Booklet, undated (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Esposito, Ronald, undated (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Estates - Eleanor Backer, undated (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Estates - Florence Cooper, undated (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Estates - Robert Frommer, undated (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Estates - Francis Lubin, undated (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Estates - Harlod Meltzer, undated (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Estates - Monticello, undated (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Ethics Ad Hoc Committee, undated (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Ethnic Articles, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - Ethnic Articles, undated (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Ethnic Bibliography, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Ethnic Diversity, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058447 9
  - Ethnic Diversity, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Ethnic Diversity - Interim Report, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Ethnic Diveristy - Drugs and Alcohol, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Ethnic Diversity - General, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Ethnic Diversity - HBCU, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Ethnic Diversity - Materials from other Institutions, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Ethnic Diversity - Minority Students, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Ethnic Diversity - Recruitment - Affirmative Action, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Ethnic Diversity - Reports, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Fifteenth Street- 312-328 East, Apartments, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Fifth Avenue - 1 Appraisal, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Fifth Avenue - 1 Management Agreement, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Fifth Avenue - 1 Offers, undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Fifth Avenue - 1 Patricia Murphy, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Fifth Avenue - 1 Patricia Murphy, undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Fifth Avenue - 1 Rentals, undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Fifth Avenue - 1 Sales, undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Fifth Avenue - 1 University Student Occupance, undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Fifth Avenue - 24 Fifth Avenue Hotel, undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Fifth Avenue - 55, 1959-1982 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Fifth Avenue - 74-76, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Fifth Avenue Hotel, undated (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Fire Deparment/Duke House, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - First Avenue - 455, undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - First Avenue - 587-589, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Fitzgerald, Julie A., undated (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Fitzgerald, Leroy, undated (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Fitzgerald, Thomas, undated (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Floyd, Billie Denelle, undated (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Forbes Lecture Series, undated (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Foreign Policy Association, undated (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Forty Third Street - 34 West, undated (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Foster, Richard, undated (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Fourth Street - 21-29 West, undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Fourth Street - 31 West, 1965-1969 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Francis, Norman, undated (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Franklin, Phyllis, undated (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - French, Stephanie, undated (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - French Cultural Mission - Whitney House, undated (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Freshman Profile, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Fullbright Scholarships, undated (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Fuller, Maria, undated (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Furmansky, Phillip, undated (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Gallatin, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058448 7
  - Gallatin, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Gallatin, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Gallatin Advisory Committee, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Gardener, Elizabeth, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Garabaldi, Antwain, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - GBA General, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - GBA Institutional Facilities, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - GBA Institutional Facilities, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - GBA Space Requirements, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - GBA Space Requirements, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - GBA Trinity Place, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - GBA Trinity Place, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Gelder Property, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - GEM program, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Georgeou, Helen, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Geriatrics, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Geriatrics Education Center Proposal, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Geriatrics and Gerontology Committee, undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Geriatrics Proposal, undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Germanacos, N.C., undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Gifts - General, undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Gifts and Grants, undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Gifts and Grants - Celdin, undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Gilbert, John, undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Gitlowe, Abraham, undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Goddard Fellowships, undated (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Going Places, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Golden, Sibyl, undated (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Golden, William T., undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Goldstein, William M., undated (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Goodwin, Robert K., undated (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Goria, Wade, undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Gorlin, Liselotte, undated (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Grace Chruch Property, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Gramercy Park West, undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Grand Union Site, undated (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Greco, Al, undated (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Greczynski, Bolek, undated (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Greenberg, Anne, undated (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Greene, Donald R., undated (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Greene Street, undated (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Greenwich Village Book Culture, undated (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Greenwood Lake, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Grey Art Gallery, undated (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Grey Art Gallery, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058449 5
  - Grey Art Gallery/Lyndell Rystrom, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Grigsby, Marshall, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Grit Proposal, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Gross, Chaim House, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Gruss, Joseph and Caroline, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Guest Housing, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Guest Suites, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Guest Suites, 1991-1994 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Guggenheim Museum, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Guzman, Anna, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Haines, Lundberg, Waehler, undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Hallowell, Burton, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Hamberger, Russ, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Hansen, Burt, undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Harckham, Laura, undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Harlem River, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Harlem River Parks Commission, undated (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Harlen River State Park, undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Harper, Michael S., undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Harrington, Christine, undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Harvard University, undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Hastings Center, undated (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Havel, Vaclav, undated (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Hayden Hall Appraisal, undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Hayden Hall Proposed Construction, undated (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Hearn, Ruby P., undated (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Heeger, Gerald, undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Heights: Appraisal Background Information, undated (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Heights: Appraisal General Correspondence, undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Heights: Appraisal Guidelines, undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Heights: Appraisal Proposals, undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Heights: Appraisal Review, undated (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Heights: Appraisal Royal Koegell, undated (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Heights: Appraisal State Budget Office, undated (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Heights: Appraisal Surveys and Title Policies, undated (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Heights: Bronx Apartment House, undated (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Heights: Campus Landmark Preservation, undated (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Heights: Closing, undated (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Heights: Comparative Values, undated (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Heights: Consent Letters, undated (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Heights: CUCF & CUNY, undated (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Heights: Cushman & Wakefield Agreement, undated (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Heights: Incumbrances, Mortgages, Etc., undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04058450 3
  - Heights: Equipment, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Heights: Equipment Exceptions, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Heights: Escrow Agreement, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Heights: Exceptions to Conveyance, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Heights: Hall of Fame, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Heights: Landauer, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Heights: Lawsuit, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Heights: Legislation, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Heights: Named Buildings, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Heights: Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Heights: O'Mara's Notes, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Heights: Operating Budget, undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Heights: Operating Information, undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Heights: PIB Merger, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Heights: Presbyterian Church, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Heights: Residence Halls, undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Heights: Schnitzer Lawsuit, undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Heights: Space Inventory, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Heights: Space and Statistical Data, undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Heights: State University, undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Heights: Technology 2 - Delay Claim, undated (Box 23, Folder 22)